https://www.biomorphdesk.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode/

COVID19 Update: Biomorph remains fully functional and continues to support the needs of our customers.
There are
items in your truck.
Truck Subtotal: $0
Recently Added Item(s)
You have no items in your truck.
ProductsErgonomic Standing DesksXO2 SeriesLevel SeriesFlexo SeriesPlus SeriesMaxo SeriesAdd-Ons & LightingCastersCPU holdersDesk spare partsFootrestsLightingMonitor ArmsPower docksRetro-Fit MotorsWire managementStorage & ExtensionsScreensCabinetsExtension Surfaces & TablesErgonomic ChairsHumanScaleHAGVia SeatingCustom OfficesApplicationsHome & Small OfficeMultimedia & DesignFlexo SeriesLevel SeriesPlus SeriesGovernment & CorporateXO2 SeriesLevel SeriesFlexo SeriesHealthcare & RadiologyPlus SeriesLevel SeriesFlexo Series
The Biomorph Difference
Visit
Customer Service
Toggle navigation
ProductsErgonomic Standing DesksXO2 SeriesLevel SeriesFlexo SeriesPlus SeriesMaxo SeriesAdd-Ons & LightingCastersCPU holdersDesk spare partsFootrestsLightingMonitor ArmsPower docksRetro-Fit MotorsWire managementStorage & ExtensionsScreensCabinetsExtension Surfaces & TablesErgonomic ChairsHumanScaleHAGVia SeatingCustom OfficesApplicationsHome & Small OfficeMultimedia & DesignFlexo SeriesLevel SeriesPlus SeriesGovernment & CorporateXO2 SeriesLevel SeriesFlexo SeriesHealthcare & RadiologyPlus SeriesLevel SeriesFlexo Series
The Biomorph Difference
Visit
Customer Service
Home
>
Privacy Policy
Customer Service
Contact Biomorph
Biomorph Privacy and Security Policy
1. Privacy Statement. Biomorph/Ground Support Equipment (U.S.) Ltd., a New York corporation operates this web site. Biomorph regards the privacy and security of user information as a critical component of the service that we offer to our users. The following information explains our information gathering and dissemination practices. 2. Price Your Own Set-Up and Request a Catalog. We use the data you send us from the Price Your Own Set-Up PO form and the Request a Catalog form to send you information about our products and to keep you informed of enhancements and complementary products in which you might be interested. We also use The PYOS system to send you invoices detailing the products you requested to purchase. You may choose to stop receiving future communications from us at any time by sending us e-mail at: unsubscribe@biomorphdesk.com3. IP Addresses. IP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to the Internet. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by our web server as part of demographic and profile data known as "traffic data" so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you. Biomorph will not use your IP address to attempt to identify your personal information. 4. System Information. System information we collect as part of "traffic data" includes time, the type of web browser being used, the operating system/platform, and CPU speed. This information is sent automatically by your web browser when you are connected to a web site. This information is used by Biomorph in identifying broad demographic trends and may be used to provide information appropriate for your computer system. You will not be personally identified from this information. 5. Sharing of Information. Biomorph feels strongly that your personally identifying data should only be seen by you, unless you authorize us to share it with others. Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, no data or information which personally identifies you will be shared with anyone. Some of your information may be shared on an aggregate basis only, as a part of a larger set of statistics (for example, statistics that indicate the percentage of our members that are female), but that information will not be sufficient to permit the recipient to identify you. Notwithstanding the forgoing, Biomorph will only disclose personally identifiable data without your permission in the following limited circumstances: (i) if Biomorph is required to do so by law, or (ii) if Biomorph has the good faith belief that such action is necessary to conform to applicable laws or comply with legal process served on Biomorph.com, or to protect and defend the rights or property of Biomorph or another subscriber or to enforce the Terms of Use. 6. Security. Information collected by Biomorph is stored in secure operating environments that are not available to the public. All of our employees and contractors are dedicated to maintaining and upholding your privacy and security and are aware of our privacy and security policies. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information within our systems, Biomorph cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.
Join the comfort club.
Copyright 2019. Ground Support Equipment (U.S) Ltd. DBA Biomorph. Biomorph and Feel Better, Work Better are regstrd. trademarks. All RIghts Reserved.
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
Site Map
